Guide to the Robert Landy Papers MC.259
New York University Archives
- Trainings -- Dr. Robert J. Landy Drama Therapy Seminar, 1995; cuid5122; 5 videocassettes (vhs) Original container for cassette MC.529.cuid5122b is labeled: Lecture: "The Image of the Mask"; and the original container for cassette MC.529.cuid5122a is labeled: LEcture #1: "Training the Drama Therapist". (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5122a-e, Box 9, Folder 16-17)
- Trainings -- Drama Therapy A - Drama Therapy W, 1998-2010; cuid5199 (Box 9, Folder 18-22)
- Trainings -- Dramaterapia, 2000; cuid5123; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5123)
- Trainings -- An early dialogue about the meaning of drama therapy, 1982; cuid5129; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5129)
- Trainings -- Ec - Is, 2002-2011; cuid5200 (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
- Trainings -- Landy at Brooklyn Preparatory School, Undated; cuid5132; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5132)
- Trainings -- Lo - N, 1994-2009; cuid5201 (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
- Trainings -- Reach for Speech, 1985-1989; cuid5126; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5126, Box 10, Folder 9-11)
- Trainings -- Res - Workshops in England, 1990-2010; cuid5202 (Box 10, Folder 12-22)
- Trainings -- Workshop in Korea, 1990-2012; cuid5131; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5131, Box 10, Folder 23)
  Label reads: Healing Ceremony / Village Ceremony by Youjin Hong July 9 90 Korea
- Unidentified video reel, Undated; cuid5186 (Box 22, Reel MC.259.cuid5186)
- Writings -- A - F, 1975-2016; cuid5193 (Box 5, Folder 1-20, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_6)
- Writings -- God Lives in Glass, 1997-2006; cuid5133; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5133, Box 7, Folder 6-16, Box 8, Folder 1-7, Box 13, Folder 43, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_4)
- Writings -- God Lives in Glass -- Children's artwork and interviews, 1998-2016 (Box 14, Folder 1-17, Box 15, Box 16, Folder 1-18, Box 17, Folder 1-5, Box 24, Folder 1-3, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_8)
  Repository permission is required for access to materials created by children and used in the creation of God Lives in Glass. Please contact the University Archives, university-archives@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2641.
- Writings -- H - Ta, 1970-2009; cuid5194 (Box 5, Folder 21, Box 6, Folder 1-23)
- Writings -- Three Approaches to Drama Therapy, 2005-2006; cuid5134; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5134, Box 6, Folder 24, Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- Writings -- Three S - W, 1982-1994; cuid5195 (Box 7, Folder 3-5)